Finding Aid for the Ken Englund Papers PASC.0157
UCLA Library Special Collections
- WACKIEST SHIP IN THE ARMY, Projects (treatments, story ideas) for film/television (Box 19, Folder 6)
  "Operation Loyalty" Storyline and Treatment by Ken Englund for March 5, 1965.
- WHITE COLLAR GIRL, Screenplays (produced/unproduced) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  First Draft Continuity by Phillip Dunne, November 28, 1941.
- WHITE COLLAR GIRL, Screenplays (produced/unproduced) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Temporary Script by Ken Englund, February 12, 1942.
- WHITE COLLAR GIRL, Screenplays (produced/unproduced) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Final Script by Ken Englund, March 17, 1942.
- WINTER QUARTERS, Projects (treatments, story ideas) for film/television (Box 20, Folder 2)
  Story outline and treatment for a love story by Ken Englund, no date.
- YELLOW NIGHTINGALE, Screenplays (produced/unproduced) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Script by Ken Englund, September 11, 1937. Property of Paramount Pictures.